<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Quests>
    <Quest>
        <Name>Clear the field!</Name>
        <Description>
           Hello! I was looking for you. Remember the scrolls I've found the other day? They seem to be from the ancient one's era, pre-cataclysm.
           Well, they seem to point to a medicine called "antibiotic". As I scientist, I can't resist wanting to know all about them. But also,
           they might help cure the plague. We couldn't save your grandparents, but maybe we can save the rest of the village.
           I believe there are more scrolls where this came from: Panambi Woods. They might contain information on antibiotics.

           As you know, it is widely believed that the ancient ones had technology beyond our comprehension, and both the Federation
           and the Sigil want to get their hands on them, and use it to win the war and further their agendas. Luckily, we
           are neutral, for now. We still might face resistance from the wild Satyr tribes.

           Take this teleporter to Panambi Woods, kill 15 Satyr, and meet with me. You'll receive 10 experience points.
        </Description>
        <DialogInProgress>
            Have you cleared the woods yet?
        </DialogInProgress>
        <DialogCompleted>
            I knew that wouldn't be a problem for a good mage like you. Now, let's get down to business.
        </DialogCompleted>
        <ExperiencePoints>
            10
        </ExperiencePoints>
        <Entity>
            rpg.game.entities.enemy.malesatyr.MaleSatyr
        </Entity>
        <EntityFriendlyName>
            Satyr
        </EntityFriendlyName>
        <ObjectiveQuantity>
          25
        </ObjectiveQuantity>
        <Giver>
            rpg.game.entities.igrenne.Igrenne
        </Giver>
    </Quest>
    <Quest>
        <Name>Knowledge is power</Name>
        <Description>
           As I told you, we need to find information on antibiotics: how do they work, and how to make them. I believe
           we will find what we need deep in the forest, north from here. Find them, and bring them back to me.
           But beware: you may find more resistance from the Satyrs. You'll get 15 experience points.
        </Description>
        <DialogInProgress>
            Have you find them yet?
        </DialogInProgress>
        <DialogCompleted>
            Amazing! Let me take a look...
        </DialogCompleted>
        <ExperiencePoints>
            15
        </ExperiencePoints>
        <Entity>
            rpg.game.entities.item.ScrollOfAntibiotics
        </Entity>
        <EntityFriendlyName>
            Scroll of Antibiotics
        </EntityFriendlyName>
        <ObjectiveQuantity>
            1
        </ObjectiveQuantity>
        <Giver>
            rpg.game.entities.igrenne.Igrenne
        </Giver>
    </Quest>
    <Quest>
        <Name>Get those rocks</Name>
        <Description>
           It looks like we are going to need some specific minerals. Luckily, I have them all in my collection.
           Now, my collection is on a tent on Golden Beach. I had to abandon the tent because it was overrun with werewolves and gorgons.
           Take this teleporter to Golden Beach, find the tent, and meet me there with the minerals.
        </Description>
        <DialogInProgress>
            Have you find those minerals yet?
        </DialogInProgress>
        <DialogCompleted>
            Good work. And now, for the last step...
        </DialogCompleted>
        <ExperiencePoints>
            15
        </ExperiencePoints>
        <Entity>
            rpg.game.entities.item.VesselOfMinerals
        </Entity>
        <EntityFriendlyName>
            Vessel Of Minerals
        </EntityFriendlyName>
        <ObjectiveQuantity>
            1
        </ObjectiveQuantity>
        <Giver>
            rpg.game.entities.igrenne.Igrenne
        </Giver>
    </Quest>
    <Quest>
        <Name>Satyr, be gone!</Name>
        <Description>
           I need to perform complex chemical operations. For that, I need some instruments.
           There is a cave in the south, which contains an ancient ruin. You should find some tools we could restore
           for our use. I'd hate having to make them from scratch. But first, get rid of the Satyrs protecting them.
           I deactivated the force field protecting the cave for you.
        </Description>
        <DialogInProgress>
            Have you find those instruments yet on the southern cave?
        </DialogInProgress>
        <DialogCompleted>
            Very good! Now, let me tell you about the instruments...
        </DialogCompleted>
        <ExperiencePoints>
            15
        </ExperiencePoints>
        <Entity>
            rpg.game.entities.enemy.malesatyr.MaleSatyr
        </Entity>
        <EntityFriendlyName>
            Male Satyr
        </EntityFriendlyName>
        <ObjectiveQuantity>
          3
        </ObjectiveQuantity>
        <Giver>
            rpg.game.entities.igrenne.Igrenne
        </Giver>
    </Quest>
    <Quest>
        <Name>No tools, no goods</Name>
        <Description>
           As I told you before, I need some instruments in order to chemically process the minerals.
           You should find them at the end of the cave you just cleared. You don't know how they look,
           so just bring everything you find that looks artificially made.
        </Description>
        <DialogInProgress>
            Have you find those instruments yet on the southern cave?
        </DialogInProgress>
        <DialogCompleted>
            Perfect, these will do just fine. Now we can finally make antibiotics and cure the plague that is
            destroying our village!
        </DialogCompleted>
        <ExperiencePoints>
            15
        </ExperiencePoints>
        <Entity>
            rpg.game.entities.item.ScientificInstrument
        </Entity>
        <EntityFriendlyName>
            Scientific instrument
        </EntityFriendlyName>
        <ObjectiveQuantity>
         4
        </ObjectiveQuantity>
        <Giver>
            rpg.game.entities.igrenne.Igrenne
        </Giver>
    </Quest>
</Quests>
